Spend a no scroll Sunday morning with
me. I fear I spend way too much time on
my phone, so I'm trying to be a little
more intentional about how I start my
day. I decided to read first thing in
the morning because I feel like I've
been slacking on that lately. And of
course, Lady had to come sit on my lap
for some cuddles. [music] After reading
a few chapters, I did my skin care and a
little light makeup because I decided I
wanted to go out for bagels and sit by
the water. Also made myself a little
matcha because there isn't a day that
goes by where I don't have one. And then
I just got dressed and ready to head
out. It felt so nice to have a little
family outing and I've been wanting to
try this [music] bagel place for so
long. We found a little spot by the
water and enjoyed our bagels. We got the
lox and it was [music] so good. It felt
so peaceful to just sit there and enjoy
the moment instead of spending my
mornings doom [music] scrolling.
Honestly, I can get used to starting my
Sundays like this.